Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed during
the filming of this series.
They beat you.
If you weren't there with the
captive commanders,
I wouldn't leave
that place in one piece, Osman Bey.
But you came just in time.
Didn't you ever think about what
if Nayman hit us both?
Martyrdom is the highest position.
May our valiants be in heaven.
Amin
We'll destroy you and your family Osman!
Stop. Stop.
Osman!
Cowards! Untie us!
Nayman will be the end of you Osman!
He'll be your end!
We'll destroy you and your family!
Is that so?
Come on!
Let us how we are going to do it!
We'll drink the blood of your sons!
We'll drink their bloods!
- Osman!
- I'll bathe in your blood!
Will you give
a duty to your children?
- You are all going to die!
- Yes.
All of you!
My Bey!
- I'll show you!
- We'll tear you apart!
- Does the traning wait for us, Bey?
- Not training.
The working man does not rust, sons.
Since the intelligence is good,
then we'll see.
Let's go! Untie their hands!
If I pity, then they become pitiful.
I won't pity them.
Thanks.
- My Bey!
- Wait.
Mashallah!
Get them and take them away.
Sons, this is how you
seem weak...
and encourage the enemy. Then,
they will make mistakes.
May you live long.
My Bey.
You put us in training without hearing
about the news we brought from Bursa.
It seems training is
more important than Bursa.
My sons are more important than the city.
First, get skilled and be strong.
Then, many cities and many
castles will be laid before you.
Now is not the time, Baysungur.
Not now.
Now, let's see how skillful
you are when you are tired.
Tell me. Tell me
about Bursa's situation.
Come here.
Bursa's Lord, Hadrat Valens.
Dear God.
Everyone around me greets you.
May your endless grace...
always be with us believers.
Amen.
Our blood sheds for God.
We live to kill the enemies of Jesus.
Welcome!
What do we know?
Nayman is a descendant of a
warrior Bey of the Belgen tribe.
His father is one of the elders of the Beys.
He was always loyal to the Khans.
So, what's the difference between
Nayman and his father?
Nayman is only loyal to himself.
And to his religion.
Nayman rebelled against Ghazan Khan...
because he led armies in
the East and the West.
He grew up but...
he always hid his real purpose.
Now he wants to destroy Ghazan.
If Ghazan Khan is blind to see this,
then he deserves to be destroyed.
Let them destroy each other, sir.
It is clear from your sentences...
that you are the one who
is blind, dear Vasilius.
Nayman will come to us.
If we don't pick the right side...
we'll be the ones who's
going to be crushed.
What about Osman? He's
fighting against Nayman.
That is the reason Nayman will
come here.
He'll want to be alliances against Osman.
We know everything about Osman's past.
What about his future? Do we
know what is he going to do?
Lord Valens.
There's no need for that.
Osman won't have a future.
Now, Bursa is under my command.
I'll bury him in to
the lands he was born.
With or without Nayman.
It's unlike the ones we've seen before.
I think those who are Lords
become commanders here, Bey.
No. They are trained
to kill all the soldiers.
Their armor is reinforced
from Constantinople.
With our current order, the
conquest is impossible.
There is system in their army, Bey.
Bursa is like that. What about the Lord?
Do you know anything about him?
We couldn't see the Lord, my Bey.
But it seems these plans are his.
He also strengthens the walls.
Catapults will not be enough.
Lord Valens is not only a commander.
He is a skillful commander
raised by Byzantium.
But Bursa is not just a city,
It has a regular army.
What troubles me...
İs being stuck between two enemies.
Baysungur.
Sons.
Now, you deserve a water.
There's news from the scouts, Bey.
Nayman has gone to the Lord of Bursa.
Really?
Gather the council at once!
Come on, sons.
What do you mean the mine is changed?
What were you doing?
We didn't understand how it happened.
It appeared when the mines cooled down.
This is not the good we brought.
Is this how you do your work?
Don't you check it?
- What is this?
- You are right, Bala Hatun.
Immediately call the person who received
this mine and the person who delivered it.
All will be questioned. This
will be solved.
Malhun. Bala.
Osman Bey is gathering the council.
Those Alps will be here until we come
back.
Did Nayman receive
that note, Celali? Are you sure?
Why is there still no news?
Our soldiers took it to him, Mother
Sultan.
Why did that Nayman attack me?
There is something odd in this.
Mother Sultan, forgive me but...
When blind people start seeing, the
first thing they get rid of is their stick.
Isn't it Nayman?
What is there to be surprised?
Apparently, he sacrificed you
after he gathered...
so many Beys behind him.
If he wanted to kill me...
he would find another
way for sure, Bayindir.
No...
You always know the best, my
Hadrat Mother Sultan.
Bayindir...
Go and check the forest..
where they attacked us.
See what happened there.
Yes, my Mother Sultan.
Celali...
Bayindir talks too much.
Ever since we left Konya, he
keeps saying...
"Nayman will kill us."
He is after something again.
- Send a man after him.
- Yes, my Sultan.
Stop.
And call Bengi Hatun.
Let's ask her if she has done
her duties.
Welcome, Commander Nayman.
The Lord is waiting for you.
Why isn't Bursa's Lord welcoming us?
Our dear Lord welcomes the ones
superior to him at the door.
Such thing has not been
done yet, Commander Nayman.
When your Lord knows me,
he will kiss my feet.
Helper...
- Take me to your Lord.
- Follow me.
We hurt Nayman greatly.
He can't even use his seal now.
This is the headquarter of Nayman.
With Beys' help...
we drew a bow here and stopped
his connection with North.
Therefore, he won't be able to
send a messenger there.
Nayman is stuck here.
Now, he will try to find
another way out.
He must have gone crazy, my Bey.
Uraz Bey.
Tell me what enemies do
when they go crazy.
They attack with all their power, my Bey.
Do you think Nayman will attack
with all his power?
If he was going to attack, we would know
his move by now.
What really worries us...
is the silence of the enemy.
Let's break the silence with the
sound of our swords, my Bey.
If he is silent, let's attack. Let's
not give an opportunity to him.
Alps want revenge.
Tell them to attack, they'll
attack, tell them to die, they will die!
Let's attack his headquarters!
Since Alps are asking for war, let's
attack them like wolves attack sheep.
- Didn't you gather the council for the war?
- Beys...
We need not only brave
men walking to death...
not only speaking men..
but also brave men
making the right moves.
Now tell me... Do you have an
intelligence to say these things?
Do you know the moves of Nayman?
- My Bey, we...
- Beys...
Nayman is stuck there.
But why didn't he attack?
Tell me, why didn't he?
Because Nayman has
another goal.
You are telling me to ride our horses
to death without knowing his goal.
Nayman went to Bursa's Lord
to ask for an alliance.
While we want to corner him between us and North...
he wants to corner us
between him and West.
Beys...
It is easy to die on a bad day.
But we will make smart moves.
We will live, and we will win.
You want a war.
* /
I will give that war to you.
But not now.
Now let's talk about why I
gathered the council.
Nayman...
went to Bursa's Lord.
We heard this from Orhan, if
Nayman and Lord agree...
let alone victory, our
existence will be in danger, Beys.
This Lord was commanding the navy
in the war between Byzantium and Venice.
He quelled many riots in west.
He won many wars.
It's not a coincidence that
they gave Bursa to him.
It’s not a coincidence that
Nayman went to him.
So, you are saying that the Lord is a
talented Commander, my Bey.
If he joins Nayman's evil
army, it won't be good for us.
Their soldiers and our Beys want war.
But Nayman is trying to build
an alliance with all his power.
What are we going to do?
What will be our move?
- How many slaves do we have?
- 12, my Bey.
- Cerkutay!
- My Bey.
So, you came here to
ask for my help, Nayman.
You will give food, water
and horses to my army.
You will give catapult
masters under my command.
And in return, you will
get so many things.
I will destroy Osman and build
an order in Konya and leave.
Or else, you will get hurt badly, Lord.
Do not compare me..
to that shepherd Osman.
That would be a big mistake.
Don't trust your walls, Lord.
Once you leave here, an arrow may...
pierce your throat.
But...
your enemy is Osman.
I am not your enemy.
The only reason of your bravery...
is the seal of Genghis.
I am the impassable
castle of Byzantium!
We've been fighting with
barbarians like you for centuries!
I can kill you here, Nayman.
But... some of the things
you said were right.
True. Osman is our
common enemy.
Working with a
barbarian like you...
will disturb me..
I will think about what you said.
You are doing the right thing
for both of us, Lord.
We could cut him into pieces with
a command of yours, my Lord.
Why did you...---
Nayman did not threaten us.
He is mad at Osman.
Why would we kill him when
we could use his anger, Leo?
Nayman will be my sword.
Cerkutay, the plan is going
to start with you.
You'll shave your beard
and paint your eyes.
You will bring Mongolian
Cerkutay back.
Your command, my Bey.
Turgut Bey.
After Cerkutay finishes his preparations,
he'll go among the prisoners.
And you'll take the caravan
where Mongolians are.
You'll lead the caravan.
When they attack the caravan, you'll
release the prisoners and come back.
- Your command.
- Cerkutay.
You'll find out...
what Nayman is doing
and what he's planning.
Your command, my Bey.
Beys.
You'll train the rest of the Alps.
You'll train an equip everyone
who can hold a sword.
From blacksmith to teachers.
Everyone.
What would a teacher do in
a battle, my Bey?
Surely, teachers will have
some difficulty at first.
But when they're trained
and assigned in the army,
they will be no different from the Alps.
I am going to march to Bursa.
If Nayman seeks an alliance,
then, I will ruin his alliance.
Come on. Everyone go
to their duties now.
Hatuns.
Tell me what the coin matter is.
They changed the mines, my Bey.
Well, Osman..
How could you even think
you could coin money?
He will learn...
that he can't move in these
lands without my permission...
and my knowledge.
I won't let him.
Well done, Bengi Hatun.
You'll be rewarded for
your work.
Thanks, Mother Sultan.
Thanks to your help.
Hatuns must be investigating the matter now.
Let them investigate.
They can't find anything.
The soldiers who helped you have
already been sent to Konya.
The rest is up to you.
I hid the real silver in the
tribe. Nobody can find it.
There's something bothering my mind.
But I will figure it out.
What is bothering you,, Bengi?
Esma.
She was in the tribe when I arrived.
She saw nothing.
But it bothered me.
I've sent my Alps to follow her.
You can't trust your luck, Bengi.
Don't let mercy
make you fail.
Intimidate her well.
- If you say you can't do it...
- I can.
I can do it.
Sit down.
Sit down here.
Attention!
My Bey, have a safe travel.
Don't be worrying about here.
We will solve the
coin matter, Inshallah.
We'll find the troublemaker.
I know, Hatuns.
May Allah protect you. Thanks.
- Come on.
What's the situation?
We're ready.
We can go when you want.
Thanks.
What's the situation?
My Bey.
The goods loaded in the
caravan going to the Lord of Bursa.
Good.
The gifts for the Lord have been loaded
in a special wagon, my Bey.
Thanks, Konur.
Turgut, when the caravan arrives, you'll
make the Alps practice.
Yes.
Come on. Everyone
get back to work.
Look, ignoble Mongolian!
Perhaps, this is the last time you
see this mansion!
Time to go, Alps.
Get up! Get up!
Get up!
Let's go.
Come back to me quickly.
Inshallah.
How do I look?
- Cerkutay.
- Yes?
Why do you look like this?
I'm going on a mission, Ülgen.
But there is something...
I need to know before I go.
Well...
I told you something.
Remember it?
Yes, I do.
Well, I need to know that.
Oh.
Cerkutay.
Well...
I love you too.
- Then...
- But...
- But?
- My mother.
The dark midwife.
She will never let me marry you.
Oh my...
Help! Mongolians
attacked the house!
Hey, stop!
Stop.
Mother, please stop!
He's Cerkutay.
It's me.
Cerkutay.
It's really you.
Mad man!
What is this?
I'm going for a mission.
Let me kiss your hand.
Well.
You're going into the
nest of the enemy, huh?
Mashallah!
Mad man!
You are crazy but you're courageous!
Well, I contributed
to your mission!
Yes, you cracked my head
open again.
Still...
What are you doing with my daughter?
Nothing, mother.
- Mother.
- Yes.
Come. Let me explain.
Well, I worked as a spy
for a really long time.
And to ask my
opinion, Cerkutay said...
"Ülgen... Sister Ülgen", he said.
- Well...
- Oh.
Ülgen!
Ülgen Hatun, we have much work to do.
I'm coming, mother.
I'm coming.
Malhun Hatun, we investigated but
couldn't find the Alps who received the wagon.
What do you mean?
You don't know them at all?
No. We saw them for
the first time there.
You delivered the mines to the men who
you saw for the first time, huh?
And you received
them?
So... Why didn't you check at all
when you received the mines?
We checked but they can't be
distinguished before melting.
Whoever did this, it must be someone
who knows the mines well.
Ismihan.
If you are behind this...
Someone must be telling
Ismihan what we are doing.
I have somebody in my mind, but...
We'll figure it out.
Find out where this mine
is mined and where this is coming from.
When we find the source,
we will find who did it.
Send Alps all around.
Obviously, the one who received the mines
changed them with the bad ones on the way.
Find those Alps! They must
have left a trace behind.
Until we find out who did this, none
of us will sleep!
Sons.
The road splits up here.
One way leads to Bursa
and the other one leads to Iznik.
I don't see separate ways, my Bey.
Both are the ways leading us to the
conquests and to our new lands.
But today you were saying
it was impossible, son.
The impossible only
takes some time, my Bey.
When we work together, we
can take any land.
Yes.
Tell me how it's going to be.
I'm listening to you.
My Bey, Bursa is ten
times as big as Inegol.
It’s not a castle but a city.
We need a regular army to conquer Bursa.
My brother and I were discussing this.
Our Alps should only engage in fighting.
They should be paid by the state.
But, sons...
You're talking about something impossible
which will take time.
Forcing tribe people to
do this is really hard.
We have to if we want Bursa, my Bey.
We need such an army to
besiege it from all directions.
That's right, sons. But...
We need to bring a new order for people.
We need to increase the taxes.
Now, tell me...
How are you going to feed the Alps?
When we get rid of the enemy
outside and the traitor inside,
we'll be powerful enough
to feed them, my Bey.
Thanks, sons.
This is your new duty.
- Your command, my Bey.
Come on! Our horses
have rested enough.
Us too.
We can't rest during the conquest.
We should arrive before the caravan.
Let's go, sons.
- Let's go!
Mother Sultan.
Nayman...
Ismihan!
What are you up to?
Why didn't you attend the council?
You attempted to kill me on the
way to the council!
Why? You got the seal first.
Then you wanted to get rid of me.
And now are you even questioning me?
If I had attempted to kill you,
you wouldn't be here now, Mother Sultan.
The arrow I shoot
always hits the target.
If wanted to kill you...
...would I come
here only with one soldier?
There is a game going on.
Obviously, it's not us who made the game.
Osman.
Your swords, Osman Bey.
Come on, sons.
You'll wait, Osman Bey.
Come over here.
Is that so? Alright.
Goodbye, Tradesman Tasinis.
Is it time, father?
We'll wait, sons.
We'll wait.
Goodbye, Commander Saneri.
You'll wait longer, Osman Bey.
Mighty Lord has more precious guests.
Is that so?
Dear Dermos, welcome.
Mighty Lord is waiting for you.
My sons.
Every leader must think about
his people first.
Let's wait for a while longer.
What is the purpose
of the Lord, father?
He thinks he
is punishing us, son.
We know our place, my Bey.
But this is too much.
I'll eventually make him pay for this.
Wait a second, son.
Hurry up!
Mighty Lord does not like to wait
for the food.
Yes, Osman Bey?
Come on, sons.
The lamb I'm eating...
is pretty delicious.
What is a shepherd who cannot do better
than to serve me in my kitchen...
doing in my presence?
I heard that you met Nayman.
That's why I'm here.
Are you questioning me just because I
meet your enemy?
I'm not going to question you.
However...
you will tell me whether you
made a deal with Nayman or not.
See? You've started questioning.
Why are your kids here with you?
Do you think I will feel pity for you...
and not kill you
while they are here?
I heard your name.
Since I heard that you won so
many battles,
I wanted my kids to meet you as well.
You know everything, Osman.
You also know that you will be ruined...
when I unite with Nayman.
Yes, tell me. What do you want?
You...
you know so little, Lord Valens.
So little.
Open them.
I said open them.
Do you think Nayman will
unite with you only for me?
You didn't care about how
small you are and you hit him well.
You made him dependent on me.
Just like you.
Of course it will be hard
for us if you unite together.
But Nayman's actual purpose...
is to lead
you into a big war.
Nayman's problem is with Ghazan Khan,
If you're going to be friends
with Nayman,
then you are going to be
the enemy of Ghazan Khan.
This has nothing to do with me.
This is about Ghazan Khan.
If you are going to oppose
the great Ilkhanids,
then, it's up to you to decide.
You can't even imagine the things...
I'll be opposing, Osman.
Let alone Ghazan Khan...
even if Genghis revives, he will
end up dead in front of my walls.
So Osman dispersed your army as well?
Osman wants me to be alone.
We will become enemies and
he will take advantage of it.
But how?
It is impossible for Osman to
know our cooperation.
They say walls have ears, Mother Sultan.
It seems Osman rules over those ears.
Osman.
You want to play games, right?
Let’s play, then.
No more games, Mother Sultan.
The more Osman tries to leave me
alone, the more I get stronger.
Lord of Bursa will obey me.
I will have a new ally.
How did you do this, Nayman?
You are settled in Konya, he is in Bursa.
He knows that he will be destroyed
if he doesn't unite with me.
Good.
Your alliance...
is my alliance.
I didn't just wait while you
were looking for allies.
I started the move that will ruin
Osman from the inside.
You, from the outside and I, from the inside...
we will destroy Osman.
I can't wait to cut
Osman's head, Mother Sultan.
Don't forget that.
How can Osman...
know our steps beforehand?
Summon...
Bayindir here.
Yes, Mother Sultan.
Bayindir.
If you betray me...
I'll bury your dead body...
all around these lands.
Do you think they take the bait?
We will see, brother.
We will see.
They can get into the
cage at any moment.
Still, keep your eyes open.
They might come out of anywhere.
If Osman Bey didn't order otherwise, I
would crush all those infidels.
Anyway, the food of the infidels is sword
and the place they will go is hell.
Be careful, Alps!
Let the game begin.
There are too many of them, Alps!
We will retreat, come on!
Save us.
You are incompetent.
But you will live and
you will serve Nayman.
Untie them! Then, take them to
the headquarters, come on!
A shepherd with fewer soldiers
than the number of his sheep,
is trying to teach me politics.
He is talking about a big war.
Who do you think you are, Osman?
I'm the one who can
see what you can't...
and knows what you don't know.
Ghazan Khan is talking to
the Altın Orda state...
and states never show
mercy to the rebels.
If you collaborate with a rebel...
you will be ruined.
This is a warning for you.
Don't side with Nayman,
and stop this bloodshed.
Or, Byzantium army...
will unite with Nayman...
and they will destroy Ghazan and you.
I will rule all the lands with
its old glory.
The seal that Nayman has
will be the end of all of us.
Mighty Lord, the messengers of
Commander Nayman are here.
You can leave, Osman.
Today, the destiny of you is up to me.
For a shepherd that
you didn't even let inside...
you lined up archers here.
Tell them to be comfortable.
Great Commander Nayman is
waiting to hear from you, Lord.
How many soldiers are there in
Nayman's army, messenger?
Thousands of soldiers are ready to
shed blood for him.
What about Ghazan Khan's army?
Ilkhanid army...
has more than thousands of men.
Being a messenger is a tough task.
Special ones are chosen.
Answer me, Messenger.
Would the seal Nayman has...
be enough to resist...
when Ilkhanids and Altın Orda unite?
I'm here to receive answer, I'm
not here to answer.
You just answered.
And this is my answer.
Is this the right decision, Mighty Lord?
Cut heads are better than
confused heads, Leo.
I will not oppose Ghazan Khan
just to destroy Osman.
When the time comes...
I'll be the one who puts an
end to the war.
Malhun Hatun, may I come in?
Come in, Esma.
What happened, Esma?
Are you crying?
What happened?
Did someone do something?
Not to me.
But those who changed the mines
which we will make the coins with...
they...
What are you saying, Esma?
We've been looking for this since morning.
Tell me what you know!
I went to Kargun tribe as Ayse
Hatun had something to send.
Bengi?
Why didn't you say it before, Esma?
I was afraid, I was so afraid.
They changed the mines.
I was afraid that Bengi Hatun
would take my sibling again.
But I couldn't stop myself, Malhun Hatun.
I couldn't.
Bengi.
Let's see what is
your excuse this time.
I'll make your life hell!
Malhun Hatun, please don't
say my name.
She'll be even angrier at me when she
hears that you've heard it from me.
I'm so afraid.
I'm thinking about my sibling's life
more than mine.
Get up, Esma.
Get up.
You are under the protection
of Malhun Hatun.
Here, take this.
Don't be afraid to use it when needed.
Be careful.
Don't wander alone, don't ever
trust anyone.
Thank you, Malhun Hatun.
Thank you.
We will be here for sure.
But...
they will be punished.
Yenişehir is this way.
Not to Yenişehir...
we're going to the cave near Günova.
My Bey.
Warriors guard there.
They’ll attack us when
we set foot there.
The number of the warriors standing
guard is three times ours, my Bey.
We can't get out without
loss if we go there.
If you give us order, let's go
there from this road.
The roads are safe and
they can't ambush.
No.
If we go that way, it
will take longer.
We'll go this way.
We won't obey them.
We'll kill them.
Now, listen to me well.
Now!
Allah is the Greatest!
You know what to do, my sons.
You're going to die...
one by one.
Alps.
Let's not keep Sultan Mesut waiting.
We're going to him now.
Bring the horses.
So, it's time for me to take
off the dervish cardigan...
and wear the royal robes, Osman Bey.
We will start a great war soon.
But Konya still supports
Nayman, my Sultan.
Supporting those who are
here to destroy these lands...
is nothing but despair, Osman Bey.
Back in the day, you came all the
way from Konya to my tribe...
just to stop me from killing Geyhatu.
That was only to avoid
more problems, Osman Bey.
I was thinking that was the
way to keep the peace.
That's what they're thinking now.
They think Konya will be saved if
they work with Nayman.
But this war is different than
any other.
It's a war between right and wrong.
He, who bows down to oppression, will
never be victorious.
You're right, Osman Bey.
I will keep your words in
mind when I sit on the throne.
My Sultan...
please don't forget about the promise
you made to support us.
I won’t.
Tell me what
our final move is going to be.
We're going to do what
we always do.
We will make our plans perfect
and attack the infidels.
I swear, Mother Sultan!
I would never betray you!
Nayman's name was the first
one that I could think of...
and that's why I said it.
I wanted to be careful.
You were only careful about Nayman, I
don't know why.
You didn't even mention Osman.
Mother Sultan..
how am I supposed to know about that
demon Osman was making such a plan?
Heathen Nayman or the demon Osman...
They're both the same for me.
I wish death for both!
My only concern is...
to protect your life!
Bayindir...
Even a single proof...
will be enough for me
to feed you to dogs.
If you betray me...
your life will be really short.
Mother Sultan...
if want to feel good...
you don't need proof.
My life is yours to take!
But..
I'm only concerned for you.
Osman clearly sent a traitor among us.
That traitor can be here among us...
but he can be next
to Nayman as well.
How are we supposed to know?
Are you saying that Osman placed...
...a Turk spy inside in the Mongol base?
No...
..not a Turk.
He might have placed a Mongolian spy there.
You know, as well as I do, Mother Sultan...
..that Nayman does not like me.
But it is not important at all.
Give me the order and I'll go into
that heathen Nayman's cave...
..and take that spy out!
I give you one last chance, Bayindir.
Cerkutay will be inside the headquarters.
And you will be the bridge between us.
Get into the Nayman’s headquarters
one way or another.
You'll be in touch with Cerkutay.
And you will sustain the
connection between us.
As you order, my Bey.
NAYMAN'S BASE
You! What is your profession?
I shoot arrows well.
-What about you?
-I'm a blacksmith.
No one is a carver?
You need a carpenter.
Why do you need one?
You! Answer my question.
You know woodcraft?
There is lots of kinds of woods.
If you want me to carve spoon.
Then, I don't know.
But if it is something big...
Take him. Take him to the carvers.
And take the others to the blacksmiths.
Get up now.
Come here.
Speak, Tendu.
The soldiers we sent to watch duty,
Osman killed them all.
Why should I care about the lives of the men,
who are not able to live, Tendu?
Is this why you interrupted my meal?
We heard nothing about them, Commander Neyman.
They still have not returned.
They will, Tendu. They will.
They might not return, Great Neyman.
What does it mean?
We've heard Osman is in Bursa.
Osman!
So, Lord has chosen his side.
I'll bury them into the same grave!
The ones, who are not with me,
are doomed to be destroyed!
Get out!
My Sultan, here.
What are these names, Osman Bey?
Soon, we'll have a great battle.
These are the names of the commanders.
My Sultan. When I appear in the battlefield,
I don't want to see these commanders in front of me.
Who would obey a dethroned Sultan while
there is an actual Sultan, Osman Bey?
No, my Sultan.
Konur, who is one of my most skilled Alps,
will be also with you. Don't worry.
He was a comrade in arms of the
many commanders here.
Of course, everyone has a difficult job, my Sultan.
Just convince a couple of Mother Sultan's
commanders, the rest will come.
When the fight begins...
...commanders will side with you Osman Bey.
Don't worry.
Those who are against you
in the battlefield...
...will side with you in Konya my Sultan.
Tomorrow will be tough.
Alps!
Search everywhere!
You know what to look for.
Look under every stone!
Mother?
Aunt?
What's going on?
What do you want Hatuns?
Do you think this is the enemy's base?
You know well what we want Bengi Hatun.
First tell me what you want.
This is not a common house.
We want this Bengi.
This.
Someone changed the raw materials of the coins.
And you thought...
..the one who did
...must be Bengi?
It's nothing to be shocked about Bengi Hatun.
You betrayed us many times before.
That is past, Malhun Hatun.
We're a family now.
Yes I made a mistake.
But you can't blame me for everything.
My mother's right.
Why didn't you tell us about this before?
We're not the enemy.
This feels like a raid.
This is about state affairs Alcicek.
We didn't want this either.
But the evidence leads us here.
Mother Bengi.
Is there anything you want to say?
I am innocent on this matter.
I didn't do anything.
Let them search.
But...
...if you're wrong...
...than this is...
...going to be your fault.
Alps! Search everywhere!
NAYMAN'S BASE
Come on.
You must work!
You must work for food!
You!
Teach them.
Go on!
So you're building catapults.
You.
Why are you stopping?
Get to work!
These catapults will be your end Nayman.
Won't you say something Aktemur?
They're doing their job.
Don't say anything, let us wait.
That's enough.
We always say nothing.
Let me tell you this.
My dad is gone.
I only have my mother.
If they can't find
what they are looking for...
If they're scapegoating my mother
for nothing then...
...I won't stay silent this time Aktemur.
Know that.
Malhun Hatun.
Your alps didn't find anything.
We'll see Bengi Hatun.
We'll see.
It's apparent.
What you're looking for is not here.
I don't have anything to do with this either.
Whomever told you this has lied.
We're related now Bengi Hatun.
We don't want to come here
like this either but...
...the information we got says
that you're behind this.
Then..
..tell me who accused me.
So that I can punish them.
It's a secret Hatun
Don't you know how state works at all?
We trust the person who gave us
this information fully.
Now tell me.
Did you do this?
You trust them fully...
...but you don't trust me is that so?
What a shame.
I don't have anything else to
say about this matter.
Malhun Hatun.
We searched everywhere, there's nothing.
Isn't it enough that you accused
my mother of being guilty?
Yes it's true.
She made mistakes before.
But she went back from those mistakes.
Why are you silent?
Speak.
Lower your voice first.
Then listen to us Alcicek.
There are things you don't know.
We didn't come here with
useless information.
Then who said what?
Let us know too.
Alcicek.
No.
It's my turn to talk this time.
Didn't my mother aid you
during your hardest times?
Didn't she save your lives?
Bala Hatun?
Is this how you repay her?
Alcicek!
I said enough.
Let her speak, Aktemur.
She's speaking the truth.
We do owe you a life..
...but that debt will not alter
our sense of justice, Alcicek.
That sense of justice..
..only seems to be working on us,
Bala Hatun.
Bengi Hatun...
...we came here just as a precaution,
searched the place and found nothing.
Thank Allah, the information wasn't true.
I don't think you should further
address the matter.
Why shouldn't I?
You destroyed our reputation.
We’re now leaving, Bengi.
I hope you have no play in this.
If you did something...
...your punishment will be great.
Alps! Prepare the horses.
My Sultan...
...the two of you
can continue from here.
If Allah permits, you'll have no troubles.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
What makes Konya strong
is the heart of its commanders.
Our cause is just.
And they will choose to support it.
Thank you.
Be ready for a war for peace...
...and a throne to bring justice.
May Allah grant you with victory.
Thanks. I hope He helps all of us.
I hope so too.
What now, my Bey?
We did our moves on
Inegol and Iznik.
It's now time for Tabriz.
What are we going to do, my Bey?
Gazan Khan is the only one who can
dethrone Sultan Alaeddin.
Once they find out what we've done...
...we'll see the outcomes.
Which Alp will be going to Tabriz?
Let's get to Yenisehir first...
...and you’ll see there.
Come here, soldier.
Where did you take my horse?
I can't find it.
Over there.
Good. Soldier!
Here you go.
Peasant..
Astagfirullah!
It's a mess here.
What's the difference between
you and animals?
Just a set of eyes in Cavuldur...
It is right sometimes,
wrong sometimes.
My Creator, make Bayindir...
...turn his back...
Turn back and...
Turn back, turn back and...
Cerkutay...
Why don't.you call me properly?
Why do you shout like this?
Come here.
I called you but you didn't hear.
Take this to Osman Bey right away.
Okay.
May Allah help you.
Wow! Wow! Wow!
My Bey, did you call me?
May Allah take you to his side
as soon as possible, Huseyin.
My Bey, I don't understand
if you say something good or bad.
When have you understood anything anyway, Huseyin?
Come on! We're leaving!
Defense is just as important
as attack in the battle, Alps!
Don't forget!
Whoever sweats a lot in training...
...bleed less in the war.
They are more in number.
Mongol cavalry...
...Byzantium infantries...
They will be relentless!
But we won't sit idle!
Come on! Get up, Alps!
Is this all you got?
Don't stop! Come on! Keep on!
We will persevere in our defense.
We won't have any martyrs
with this-defense order, InshAllah.
And every infidel stepping on
these lands will know that...
...if any of them takes a single step on these lands,
which we turned into our motherland with our blood...
...we will make them
experience the hell itself!
Come on, Alps!
Keep on! Come on
This defense is unbreakable.
We stand like a castle, Turgut Bey.
Thank you, Songur Agha, thank you.
We will have many victories
with this order, Turgut Bey.
I don't want any mistake, Gurbuz,
we'll train more.
The motherland is inside a circle of fire.
And an unmatched war is waiting for us.
I won’t let any more of my valiants die!
Come on, Alps! Come on!
The army of the believers is
being raised, my Sheykh.
You think while the infidels
unite the believers sit idle?
Let them unite, of course.
Tell me.
What duty do you have for your Sheikh?
My Sheikh.
I was going to talk about this matter.
Let the Bey order.
I'll accept it with the utmost respect.
It is a matter of state after all.
Astagfirullah. Astagfirullah.
My Sheikh.
In order to beat the enemy...
...you need to go to Gazan Khan.
He needs to make a move in Konya.
Or, neither will we be able to
enthrone Sultan Mesud....
...nor will we be able to challange the enemy.
Dervish will set out right away.
We will arrive Tebriz soon,
if Allah permits.
What is the gold bar for?
It will ease our way..
...and it will be the evidence for the letter,
which will be taken to Gazan Khan.
Alright, but...
...I have a condition.
Tell me, my Sheykh. Tell.
The one who sets out shall reach
his destination in the most beautiful way.
You'll make me do what I wanted to do earlier
with your order.
I'll go to Beyt-ul Haram.
I'll fulfill my duty of pilgrimage
to Makkah, Osman Bey.
My Sheykh,
include us to your prayers.
My Sheykh. You've shed light onto
my way all these years.
Pray in the shadow of the Kaaba
for our holy cause.
Come on, then.
I'd better hit the road!
The time is going against us.
We need to send the news
to the Dervish right away.
- Sure, my Sheykh, sure.
-Let's go.
You said nothing, Aktemur!
Aren't you the Bey of this tribe?
They searched your tribe
and you said nothing!
What could have I done, Alcicek?
They said they had information!
What if they found it in our tribe?
But it wasn'tJthe case!
They couldn't find anything, Aktemur!
They trampled us again, Aktemur!
They humiliated us again!
Alicicek! Pull yourself together!
Everyone does their duty.
You also know that Bengi Mother
and Ismihan are still together.
I know, of course! I know!
But why are they together?
Don't you see why my mother acts with that woman?
Why does she do it, then?
Your family!
Your family doesn't stand by my mother!
And my mother is looking for
someone she can lean on!
My children!
Calm down.
Daughter.
Aktemur.
Don't.
What can we do mother Ayse?
You saw what happened.
I only have my mother.
This upsets me so much.
I know my sweet girl.
But you should know that...
...no matter what happens
between families...
...don't let it trouble you.
Are you going to fall in the first wind?
You'll see many troubles and many fights.
Don't frown!
Smile.
Aktemur. Come on. Smile!
Don't just fake it.
Smile like you mean it.
Don't fool me.
I'm not a kid.
I said smile.
Did you gather around...
..for everyone that left?
This is an affair of the state.
And it's also..
Muslim's duty.
Father.
May. Allah keep you safe.
Come back soon, if Allah permits.
We're responsible for conquests sweetheart.
Victory...
....and return is only knowm by Allah.
May Allah keep you safe my Sheykh.
Thank you my shehzade.
My shehzades.
Keep each other safe.
Always stay in the path of Allah.
That path will lead to victory.
My Sheykh.
May Allah protect you.
Thank you my girl.
My Sheykh.
Take care.
Thank you Osman Bey.
Come on.
Thank you.
May Allah protect you.
No!
May Allah protect you my Sheykh.
Take care my Sheykh.
No.
My Boran.
Believe in Allah...
...to keep me safe.
Our path is full of his protection.
Okay my Sheykh.
May Allah protect you.
Thank you.
-May Allah bless you all.
-Ameen.
May you always walk towards Allah.
Ameen.
May Allah keep you right.
Send my regards...
..and my advice to those
I couldn’t bid farewell.
If they'll walk with us in this path...
...they'll find us.
Take care.
Kumral.
Why don't you take me, my Sheikh?
Don't you think I am one of your Dervishes?
I can go because you're here Kumral.
How can I go if there's no one
to take care of our state?
In the name of Allah.
Now...
...the post is yours.
And the sweater is yours.
My Sheykh.
But...
Can I carry it?
If Allah permits, you can.
Touch people.
Touch many hearts.
We need those who have burning hearts, Kumral.
Even water burns for Allah my Sheykh.
Stay safe.
Take care.
Kumral Abdal.
My Sheykh.
Let it be blessed.
Your path shall be open, my Sheykh.
I told you.
Bengi Hatun.
I told you to take care of Esma!
They couldn't find anything.
I made them move the silver somewhere else
out of the tribe in case Esma told them.
Not enough!
That's not enough!
Just like how I silenced her before...
..I'll do now too.
Don't doubt it.
I'm going to send her away with her sibling.
I have it from now on.
If she was scared of you
like she used to be...
...she wouldn’t be able to
say even one word.
Send that Esma to me
as soon as possible.
I'm going to scare her.
I can handle it.
Don't make me say it twice Bengi.
Send that Esma to me as soon as possible.
Are the alps ready?
They will be, if Allah permits.
I know how that lowlife
Nayman will attack us like a rabid dog.
But we'll defend.
With Allah's permission we won't break down.
We'll take care of him.
Nayman is cornered.
The field he will be destroyed
shall be decided soon.
EyvAllah..
May I my bey?
Tell me. Tell me.
Ismihan.
She got suspicious of Bayindir.
But we won't reveal Bayindir.
We won't stop being cautious.
Cerkutay is saying that
Nayman is building catapults.
He even...
..sent the drawing of it.
There.
He's going to attack Yenisehir.
So he was waiting for the catapult
to be done huh?
Now I understand
what he was waiting for till now.
This catapult is huge.
If they take Yenisehir the beys near
the skirt will fall too Osman Bey.
I don't want to say it but..
...so will the feeling of
freedom within the Turks.
Will we allow the catapults
to be built my Bey?
As long as Cerkutay is there...
...we will never let that happen.
Cerkutay will stay there.
I have more orders for him.
Nayman...
We now know all the moves you made
and are going to make.
Let's see what you'll do now.
Are the catapults here?
They're.
They're ready.
There's word from the guards Nayman.
Osman's Sheykh Edebali
is going on a journey.
Osman.
Soldiers!
Get ready.
We're going to go and end
Osman's source of light.
He's trying to combine
all the catapults we have made...
..into one.
This one..
...worths ten of ours.
But to take a catapult
this big to the walls...
Wouldn't that be a handicap for them?
Nayman saw that he won't be
victorious on the battlefield.
As it looks...
...he wants to attack our castles and inns.
Osman Bey this...
This means a power we can't stand against.
Do you think that lowlife Nayman
will be successful?
No.
Orhan.
You were saying that they strengthened
Bursa's walls right?
Yes my bey.
But I also said our catapults
can't destroy it.
But...
But these can.
If we can destroy these catapults...
..and..
..build the same ones..
...then we'll be the ones
who have the advantage.
And therefore...
...Kopruhisar, Koyunhisar, Iznik...
and even Bursa's doors
will open up to us.
If Allah permits.
Then you're saying that we're going to
take the catapult Nayman has.
Yes.
Once Cerkutay completes
the rest of his mission...
My Bey.
Nayman has left his headquarters
with his warriors.
They're going towards the route
our Sheikh has taken.
What?
My Sheikh...
My father!
-Osman..
-Calm down.
I will destroy all of them if they hurt him.
I'll go with you.
-Boran!
-My Bey.
Prepare the Alps!
Okay, my Bey.
Alps, we're leaving!
Come on!
Let's go
I didn't come here to grow crops...
...I came here to fight.
But who are we going to side with?
That's the question.
Both Nayman and Osman
want us on their sides.
But...
What do they have in common?
Do you know that?
They're both greedy enough to
first ask for our support...
...then go after Bursa.
But there's something that they're missing.
Bursa can't be conquered.
There's no doubt about that.
Nayman says that he will march on Tabriz.
...once he destroys Osman.
Nayman is stuck here.
He needs us.
What about Osman?
We can destroy Osman with a single move.
But...
..if what he has said
turns out to be true...
...we will have strengthen Nayman.
Who are we going to choose?
Bursa, an example of balance...
...and a Bursa,
a place that's impenetrable.
I'm not going to rush to make a decision.
I will visit Nayman and Osman...
...on their own property.
I will see how they're doing
on their own lands...
..and then make a decision.
Welcome, Malhun Hatun
Thank you, Ulgen.
Tell Esma to come see me.
Esma?
She left.
Where did she go?
To Sogut.
Alcicek called her there.
What business Alcicek might
possibly have there?
Did she go on her own?
Oh, Esma
I told you not to trust anyone!
Alps, prepare my horse!
What is Alcicek Hatun doing in Sogut?
Why did you call me here?
I don't know about that, sister Esma.
Go away.
So, Esma...
Bengi Hatun...
Why couldn't you keep your mouth shut?
What are you going to do to me?
Why would I do anything?
Mother Sultan called you here.
But you need to listen to me first.
Just agree to everything
Mother Sultan has to say.
Okay?
I will make sure you and
your sister get away from here.
Don't do this, Bengi Hatun.
Don t do this.
Don't be afraid.
Just do what I told you to do...
...and agree to what Mother Sultan says.
Okay, daughter?
Okay.
Let’s go.
Protect our Sheikh!
They are too many of them,
my Sheykh! Get away from here.
We're not going to run!
We're going to fight back!
Today is the day we become martyrs!
Attack!
Allah is Everlasting!
Are you afraid of me, Esma?
You are.
You are, of course.
Then, why couldn't you hold your tongue?
Why did you tell
everything you see to Malhun?
She'll say nothing about this matter
from now on, my Sultan.
And she'll avoid Malhun.
And I'll send her away from here.
Right, Esma?
Yes.
I made a mistake. I owed Malhun Hatun.
I owed for the life of Orhan Bey.
I did it for it, or...
Osman rebels, Esma.
I rule over these lands, not him.
And what is he doing?
He dares to make coins
without my permission!
You think I can allow this?
Does this dagger belong to you?
It's a gift from Malhun Hatun.
Can I come in, Mother Sultan?
Come in, Celali.
Malhun Hatun is coming, my Sultan.
Celali.
Bengi Hatun.
You go out.
I said go out, Bengi Hatun.
Come on, Hatun! Didn't you hear?
So, it was a gift for your talking.
Seems like expensive.
Befits to Malhun.
Mother Sultan! What have you done?
What have you..
..done?
Ismihan.
Ismihan Sultan.
Come here Malhun.
Come.
Mother-
Esma.
Esma what happened?
Hang on.
Hang on Esma. Hang on. Hang on.
Hang on Esma.
Esma.
I bear witness that..
...there is none worthy of worship except Allah.
Esma.
I bear witness that..
...Mohammad is His servant and messenger.
Esma.
Ismihan.
Ismihan Sultan.
Malhun Hatun.
What have you done
Soldiers!
Arrest Malhun Hatun
You'll die today Edebali.
And Islam will die with you.
Death is our Shahada!
I'm here my Sheykh!
Thank Allah.
Allah.
Allah, in the name of Allah.
My Sheykh.
Shaman.
Come here.
Shaman or whatever you are!
Shaman.
Get up.
Leave, great Nayman!
Shaman.
Tengri(Turkish-Mongolian God)
will bless you with revenge.
So you tried to kill my Khan, my Sheykh.
I am going to be your wrath now.
So you tried to end the source of my light?
Here you go.
I'm going to take you darkness from you.
Osman don't.
Shaman.
I swear for this I'm going to take your
people from you Osman.
I'm going to take those you love from you.
Do your best.
Soldiers!
We're going back!
Move.
My Sheykh.
It's not important Osman Bey.
It will just make me perform ablution at best.
My Sheykh.
Father don't travel like this.
Let's go to Yeniseh
and get it checked.
There's no turning back now, my child.
We’ll keep going.
I was afraid that you'd leave
without saying goodbye, my Sheykh.
But seeing you now makes me feel good.
He who wanted to say goodbye
should have found me before I left.
There's no goodbye after that.
He who finds us on the road
can only be a comrade.
My Sheykh...
...is that what you wish?
What is it, Osman Bey?
It's whatever my Sheykh says, Turgut Bey.
If you wish to go with him...
...I'd feel good about his well-being.
I would feel at ease.
I only have one condition..
Do you give your blesings to
Turgur Bey, brother?
I do.
You give me your blessings too.
You'll always have my blessings.
Our tribe owes you a lot.
I'm always at my homeland's service.
Now, it seems that,
I'll oversee this mission...
..while you oversee home, brother.
Eyvallah.
Good luck.
Will you give me your blessings, alps?
We will, my Bey!
Brother..
Let’s go.
Farewell.
Farewell, farewell.
My Sheykh
Mother Sultan arrested
Malhun Hatun, my Bey.
For what reason?
They say that she tried to kill her.
What?
They're attacking us from all sides!
I will cut the tongue that lies
about my family, my Hatun!
It is a matter of time!
All of them will share the same end!
Alps!
Bring my horse!
Visit our website for more: turkision.com